Register of the Center for the Study of Popular Culture Records
Hoover Institution Archives
- Review of Odyssey: From '60s Radical to '96 GOP Delegate by Gerald F. Seib, Wall Street Journal, 1996 August 13
- A Small Town in the Big City: A History of Sunnyside and Woodside--Booklet, 1976 June
- Norway--Brochure, clippings, issues of Liberal Debatt, letter, press release, and review of "A Policy of Misunderstanding," by Philip G. Altbach, 1962-1968 (Box-folder 118: 1)
- San Francisco Focus interview of David Horowitz and Peter Collier by Ken Kelley, undated. (Folder 118: 2)
  Includes a letter to David Horowitz from J. B. Esterkin, Prime Properties, 1985 February 2
- Personal correspondence, 1961-1964 (Folder 118: 3)
- "Chinese stuff,", 1962. (Folder 118: 4)
  Includes article, letter, and notes in Chinese
- Miscellany, 1959-1998.
  Announcements of speaking engagements; class assignments; evaluation of students' papers; itinerary; letters; notes; papers by Philip Horowitz; personal letters and greeting card; report on teaching materials; schedule; typescript copy of Student: The Political Activities of the Berkeley Students; and writings by an unidentified individual
- Personal letters, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 119: 1)
- Memoranda to Adam Bellow about Radical Son, and notes relating to his manuscript, and David Horowitz's personal feeling towards his parents possibly to be used in the book, 1994-1995 (Folder 119: 2)
- Complimentary letters regarding Radical Son, other books and projects, 1997-1998 (Folder 119: 3)
- Correspondence with The Nation; review of the Free World Colossus by Arnold S. Kaufman and letters relating to it; and reviews of books by David Horowitz and other writers, 1964-1966 (Folder 119: 4)
- Hadassah Jewish affairs--Clippings, 1945-1947 (Folder 119: 5)
- Swedish articles, 1962-1963. (Folder 119: 6)
  Articles in English and Swedish, clippings, letters, and papers by students
- Miscellany, 1967-1979. (Folder 119: 7)
  Brochure, clippings, and letters
- Ramparts, 1970-1974
- "Marxism and Its Place in Economic Science," by David Horowitz, Berkeley Journal of Sociology, 1971-1972
- David Horowitz's Long March," by Scott Sherman, The Nation, 2000 July 3
- Correspondence relating to the Free World Colossus, 1963-1965
- Articles by others (Box 120)
  - The Public Interest, 1990-1998
  - The Concord Review, 1997
  - American Experiment Quarterly, 1998
- Courses offered at various academic institutions and activities of students, 2003 August - September
- Articles, 2004
  by Sara Hebel and David Horowitz
- 3 3.5-inch diskettes, undated
- 1 zip disc, undated
- 2 compact discs, undated
- List of Wednesday Morning Club guests, 1997 February 3 (Box-folder 121: 1)
- Invitations, 1997 January – May (Folder 121: 2)
- Wednesday Morning Club--Barnes and Goldsmith, 1996 January 24. (Folder 121: 3)
  Clippings, guest list, and letters
- Michael Ovitz, 1998 June 9. (Folder 121: 4)
- Angus Mackay, 1997 April. (Folder 121: 5)
  Includes biographical note, invitation to and details of luncheon and other related materials, and a passport photograph of Angus Mackay
- William Schneider, 1996 November 18. (Folder 121: 6)
  Announcement, biographical note, clipping, list of guests, and text of political commentary
- Wednesday Morning Club planning/strategy with show coalition, 1996 September 10. (Folder 121: 7)
  Clippings, financial records, list of suggested speakers, and miscellany
- List of potential speakers--Requests denied, 1998-1999 (Folder 121: 8)
- John Zogby, 2000 January 19. (Folder 121: 9)
  Letter of invitation to speak and related materials. Includes 1 photographic print depicting John Zogby
- John Irving, 2000 January 24. (Folder 121: 10)
  Announcement of a luncheon featuring John Irving and miscellany
- Invitations sent out to individuals to speak at various events at the Center, 1997-1999
- Kasich/School on Wheels, 1998.
  Lists of invitees, record of expenses, and related materials
- Miscellany., 2002-2004
  Includes writings by others, report of the educational programs at the Center and other academic institutions, registrations, and related materials,
- Robert Bork--Breakfast, 1996 October 9. (Box-folder 122: 1)
- Max Cleland--Campaign, Georgia, 1996 June. Announcement of a speech by Max Cleland and articles by David Horowitz, Los Angeles Times, 1996 February – June. (Folder 122: 2)
  Includes organizational structure and membership information, Center for the Study of Popular Culture, undated
- Wednesday Morning Club--Club Buzz articles, 1996. (Folder 122: 3)
  Includes lists of names, undated
- Town Hall Los Angeles, 1998 (Folder 122: 4)
  Brochures; list of events, corporate patrons and speakers who have addressed Town Hall Los Angeles; and mission statement
- Writers Guild of America, West (WGA), 1998. (Folder 122: 5)
- Correspondence of David Horowitz, 1997 (Folder 122: 6)
- List of special invitees, 1998. (Folder 122: 7)
  Includes George Bush, Newt Gingrich, and Orrin Hatch
- Orrin Hatch event, 1997 April 18. (Folder 122: 8)
  Biographical note, list of publications, expense records, and related materials
- Christopher Cox, 1997 January (Folder 122: 9)
  Biographical note, list of legislative accomplishments, clippings, and miscellany
- Spencer Abraham, 1997 January. (Folder 122: 10)
- Biographical note on Ruben Barrales, Lionel Chetwynd, John McCain, Richard Burke Noonan, Fred Thompson, and others (Folder 122: 11)
- Original forms--Fax cover sheet, undated (Folder 122: 12)
- Membership drive, 1998. (Folder 122: 13)
- Wednesday Morning Club (WMC) ideas, 1997. (Folder 122: 14)
- List and stationery, undated (Folder 122: 15)
- Monty Warner File, 2000. (Folder 122: 16)
  Constituent names and addresses
- Wednesday Morning Club (WMC)--Letterhead, undated (Folder 122: 17)
- Foundation Francisco Marroquin, 1998. (Folder 122: 18)
  Brochure, clippings, and invoice. Includes a proposal for a joint event with Wednesday Morning Club, 1998
- Operation Hope, 1997. (Folder 122: 19)
  Biographical information on John Bryant, chairman and chief executive officer, and correspondence with the Center for the Study of Popular Culture
- State Department Watch, 1998. (Folder 122: 20)
  Articles, including one by Arch Puddington, invitation to lectures, and letter
- Wednesday Morning Club (WMC)--Miscellany (pending), 1997 (Folder 122: 21)
- Book order forms, undated (Folder 122: 22)
- Events--RSVP forms, undated
- Split Wizard report, 1999
- Miscellany, 2001
- Press clippings, 1994 (Box-folder 123: 1)
- Whidbey Island Films, 1994. (Folder 123: 2)
  Biographical information on Fred Barnes, Lionel Chetwynd, Morton Kondracke, and Ted Steinberg. Includes budget summary and proposal
- David Horowitz's faxes, undated (Folder 123: 3)
- Letter from Glenn C. Moret to Robert Schnereger, 1994 March 25, requesting him to reverse the verdict of the hearing conducted by the review panel, University of Southern California, concerning Stephen Charles Hollingsworth (Folder 123: 4)
- Clippings and articles, 1994, relating to questions of black anti-Semitism and other political issues; role of media, music, and film industry; health plans; and propagation of conservative ideas.
  Includes 1 3-3.5-inch diskette
- Clippings, 1994 (Box-folder 124: 1)
- Miscellany, 1993-1994.
  Includes annual report, articles, brochure, book review, journal, letters, memoranda, and report relating to various social, racial, and gender issues, and to the role in society of the media and the student community. Also includes a mission statement from the Individual Rights Foundation